ANJUSHA THEKKUMKATTIL SHAJU



CONTACT

anjusha.tshaju@gmail.com

Sermany - 45141

in Anjusha T.S

SKILLS

Languages Malayalam

English

German

Technical Skills HTML/CSS **JavaScript Typescript Angular React JS React Native** Node Js **Express** Java **Spring boot PHP** Python **Firebase** MySQL **DynamoDB PostgreSQL MongoDB** GraphQL **AWS Services** GIT **GitHub Bitbucket** Docker **Unit Testing** Mocha Chai **Operating Systems** Linux macOS Windows

SUMMARY

Experienced Full Stack developer with more than 4 years of hands-on experience in designing, developing, and implementing applications and solutions using a range of technologies and programming languages. Capable for analyzing customer feedback in order to find the best way to create new and enhance the existing product features, and testing and debugging the software to keep it optimized.

WORK HISTORY

m 06/2022 - Present

Full Stack Engineer ♀ Conceptboard Cloud Service GmbH Stuttgart, Germany

- · Designing and implementing scalable web services, applications, and APIs
- Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade software
- Writing technical documents.

6 05/2021 - 06/2022

Working Student Software Developer

♥ Funanga AG Berlin, Germany

- · Writing and implementing efficient code
- · Fixing and improving existing software
- Produce clean, efficient code based on specifications.

1 01/2018 - 12/2020

Q Zeefasys Pvt.ltd India

Full stack developer

• Developing and implementing the front-end and back-end portions of an application.

- Build reusable code and libraries for future use
- Identified and suggested new technologies and tools for enhancing product value and increasing team productivity.

1 01/2017 - 01/2018

Paract Software Solutions Pvt.ltd India

Software Developer

- Optimize applications for maximum speed and scalability.
- · Collaborate with teams and stakeholders
- · Developed new user-facing features.
- Ensuring user experience determines design choices

EDUCATION

1 07/2012 - 04/2016 Anna University Chennai, India

Bachelor of Engineering

• Electronics and communication CGPA: 7.46.

EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

- Participated in the "4th National Conference on Communication, Electrical and Electronics System".
- Published My Project Paper in "International Journal of Research in Electronics (IJERT)".